or even during September,
October when it's rainy season.
I enjoy myself the most, I think, because
I love when it's cold and
chilly and you can just go out
for a walk or play outside with your
friends. I think that's
when I enjoy it the most.
Has the weather
changed much in recent years?
I would say drastically, yes. It's gotten
hotter and hotter and humid.
I think because of global warming, it's
been really bad lately.
Would you say the weather in your
hometown is suitable for working?
I mean around December, yes. But
throughout the year,
no, it's very, very hot.
Back in India, it's like when you get
out, it's a lot of humidity and you just
don't feel your best.
The TV documentary that I watched was a
documentary on the artist Eminem.
He goes by the name Marshall Matters. And
I remember I was very
young when I watched it.
The reason I love it is because it's very
inspiring because in the movie,
he shows all of his struggles and the
poverty that he went through.
He was very unfortunate as a child and
even when he was a teenager.
And that goes to show how much
determination he had towards his dreams
and his plans and goals
of the future that he knew that he was
going to make it big
in the music industry.
And now he's known to be one of the
biggest musical artists in the industry.
I learned inspiration from that movie. I
think it gives you a lot of motivation
every time you watch it.
It goes to show that no matter where you
come from, no matter how
small your hometown was
or how many obstacles you had in life,
but still you can make it big.
And it also goes to show that you just
have to be passionate about what it is
that you want in your life.
And through that, you can achieve the
greatest things and you can surpass
even your highest levels of insecurities
and doubts that you have
and the fears that you have.
And he's also like one
of my favorite artists.
So to see him go through that really
inspires you and shows you that you can
do it no matter what it is.
That it's usually self-doubt which keeps
you from chasing your dreams or from
achieving your goals.
But in that movie, it's shown that you
can really do whatever you want.
So we've been talking about a TV
documentary that you watch them.
We're going to continue to talk about TV
programs and TV advertising.
Do you think that there are too many game
shows on TV nowadays?